WOMAN: Where are you going?
MAN: Just gonna take a look around outside.
(Sheldon:)Bad idea.
WOMAN:
No, Jim, don't open the door.
(Sheldon:)Listen to her, Jim.
[DOOR CREAKS ON VIDEO]
MAN:
Don't worry. There's no one out there.
[SCARY MUSIC PLAYS AND
WOMAN SCREAMS ON VIDEO]
[KNOCKING]
SHELDON: Leonard and Penny.
Leonard and Penny. Leonard and Penny.
LEONARD:
Who is it?
All right. We've got a titanium deadbolt
and a reinforced jam controlled by...
(Howard:)...a state-of-the-art
electronic access system.
(Sheldon:)-What if they cut the power?
-There's a 200-watt...
(Raj:)-...uninterruptible backup power supply.
-If someone steals my keys?
(Raj:)There are independent voice
and fingerprint scanners.
What if somebody kidnaps me,
records my voice...
(Sheldon:)...and then cuts off my thumb?